As we all travel across the
sea Raising our voices We
take in the beautiful blue
world Our spirits ready to
go Everybody rejoices Now
let's go get the sails all
yeah Here we are in between
the sea and the sky Ready
now for adventure We're
itching to try Get ready to
roam So all aboard now We're
set to go Set sail to the
ocean so deep Ready for a
truly grand adventure Well,
don't you think That sounds really
fun All this excitement Second to
none As we all travel across the sea
Raising our voices We take in the
beautiful blue world Our spirits ready
to go Everybody rejoices Now let's
go get the sales all unfurled La la
yeah If there's something
that I just won't
ever forget It's the way that I felt when
our journey was set Now
I won't be scared As
long as I keep that
feeling there With that,
let us keep up the pace While
enjoying every trip from place to
place Our timid hearts get the
rhythm ingrained So let's keep going,
adventure awaits So many treasures
await So now let's raise our voices
in pride Laughing out when they are
found With all the riches in hand,
everybody rejoices Party on,
cause we stand tall and proud
Life is adventurous, be aware it's
dangerous Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you now, fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
She's so brutal.
It's like she's some kind of
crazy fire redeeming woman.
And I know we said way too much.
Don't forget, Mistress
Perona loves treasure too.
That's right, she'll never
take it away from her.
Still, I wish we hadn't
told her about the shortcut.
We messed up.
That cheeky little brat.
How dare she try to take my treasure?
And she wants to steal the Sunny, load
it up, and use it as her getaway boat?
Sorry, sweetie, you don't
know who you're messing with!
I've got to hurry and
get back to the Sunny!
Hold on, what's up with this weird bridge?
It doesn't look like
everything else around here.
It's narrow, but it's really well made.
Stupid bastards!
That's it!
No one ate it!
Holy crap!
I didn't see anything!
Oh, now you've done it!
When I get up, I'm gonna stop
you Pipsqueak parents flat!
There won't even be more flat to bury!
Oh crap, this guy is seriously
pissed off! This is bad! Really bad!
Here he comes!
What the hell?
Dammit, I can't move!
My eyes are stuck on the ground!
This sucks!
Oh, you're stuck, huh?
Maybe he always just likes
screaming when he's kicking ass.
I mean, come on, it's not like he
could actually be losing, right?
Cut it out!
Retreat! All right.
These guys are like little demons.
Guess that wasn't enough to keep him
down from what I've seen even though He's
big and red and all this guy still has
traces of Luffy's personality left in it?
What are you talking about?
He already told us he didn't recognize any
of us and that Moria was his master Yeah,
but even so
Check it out! Look!
There's a huge hunk of meat!
Hunk of meat?
Necroze!
He's halfway down, cut it as three.
Even if there were rules, I don't
think this guy would follow him.
All right!
He's down again after
a blow to the kneecaps!
Yeah!
Keep it up, you guys!
Just stall him till the captain
beats the crap out of Merde!
Hurry up and get those
shadows back, Straw Hat!
There's no reason to keep
screwing around like this.
Let's put him down for good.
Hold on!
I thought the idea was for
us to keep this big monster
busy to make sure he doesn't
get in Straw Hat's way!
There's no way we can
beat this thing, man!
There wasn't any meat!
You tricked me!
I built my kneecaps!
A fight isn't truly over until you've won!
It's not just a giant, he's a zombie!
To beat him, you're
gonna have to purify him!
That's right, Zoro!
We're just buying time!
Take it easy!
You don't want to help, stand back!
I don't feel like waiting
around for Luffy to win, either.
A dinosaur could step on this blade
and it wouldn't bend a millimeter.
They say that hardness is the greatest
characteristic of a black blade.
With Chouchou here, I've finally
gotten my hands on a first-rate sword.
And I think this is a perfect
time to try it out. Stop it!
Why you gotta be so stubborn?
Just let Lock beat Moria!
Stop right there!
Who is that? What does she want?
It's that pirate woman.
What do you think you're doing with
all that treasure I was gonna steal?
And what are you doing on board the Sunny?
I was worried there for a
second, but it's only you.
How'd the wedding ceremony
with Absalom go over already?
Oh, give me a break!
Who would ever want to marry
that invisible pervert beast man?
And I take it you managed
to escape the wedding.
Absalom can't do anything right.
So, what are you gonna do?
As you surmised, I do plan on stealing
your ship to escape from Thriller Bark,
and I'm bringing all the treasure with me.
If you try to stop me, I'll fight you.
And you won't like that.
You're not very strong,
so the mini-hollow ghost army will
be more than sufficient against you.
The only one among you that put up a fight
against me was that
depressing long-nosed guy
Who is that
Just who in the hell are you
We don't know him,
but he's definitely an enemy
just now He made some of our
brothers vanish without a trace
right before our very eyes.
He's the ordinary man.
He's dangerous Whoever
he is, he's bad news
Vanished?
It can't be. I think. I think.
I know who this man is.
It's him.
One of the seven warlords of the sea.
The tyrant, Bartholomew Kuma.
The atrocities he committed when he
was a pirate are beyond the pale.
One of the seven warlords on the sea?
What's a guy like him doing
here on Thriller Bark?
You've got to be kidding.
Do you work for Moria? What?
Master Moria?
I was, but I'm not anymore.
I've had enough of this.
I'm just trying to
escape from this island.
I want no part of it.
If you could take a vacation,
where is it you'd like to go?
He's making small talk.
This is not the time or
place for such nonsense.
But if I were to go on a vacation,
somewhere dark and damp, Somewhere
with an old, creepy castle.
I'd spend every day there
singing a song of curses.
She answered!
That's the ghost princess for you.
I agree.
We loved your answer, Mistress Verona.
I got caught up in my daydream.
Stop screwing around.
I admit I was taken aback
when I realized who you were.
But I've got nothing to fear.
With my Devil Fruit powers, there's no one
I can't take down, and that includes you.
Are you listening to me?
I'd imagine your shadow is
pretty strong, isn't it, Kuma?
Good.
Then I'll take it from you as a
parting gift to my former master Moria.
So prepare yourself!
Negative ghost!
And special hollow!
All right!
There it is!
Mistress Perona's ultimate combo!
Before you interrupted
with all that yelling,
I was simply going to
ask you where Moria is.
Where did she go?
Mrs. Perona!
What was that? I'm scared!
She disappeared!
What about you?
What did you do with Mrs.
Perona, you bastard?
Unforgivable!
Where's our princess?
You're gonna pay!
You're the cat burglar, aren't you?
One of the Straw Hat Pirates.
I've heard that Monkey D.
Luffy has an older brother.
Is that true?
No way!
He just suddenly appeared up there.
Did he teleport?
Yeah, he does.
You're talking about Ace, right?
Why do you want to know?
I see.
So the rumors are true.
Yeah, so?
What's all this about?
What do you want?
Are you really a warlord?
What I'm doing here is
none of your concern.
That guy is bad news.
What does he want with Luffy?
I've got to go warn him.
Got you Maria.
You're mine.
You're not getting away.
This time you bastard.
I'm gonna beat the crap out of you.
Give everyone shadows back.
Now gong gong.
Oh, damn it!
He tricked me!
Hey, hold on!
Don't ignore me, you dumb shadow!
No, come back!
Or at least tell me where the hell I am!
Hey!
Oh man this sucks
everybody's counting on me to
beat moria and get their
shadows back for them?
And I gotta do it by sunrise wait why
do we need our shadows back by then?
Oh yeah the sun's gonna
melt us we're gonna be
dust if I can't work
this out before morning!
This is bad!
I've been gone too long already!
You want a real fight?
Looks like you found one!
Let's see what you got!
Didn't notice it earlier, but Shusui's got
a lot more heft to it than my Yubashiri.
Never used a black blade before.
Zoro, get out of the way!
But with this weight...
Awesome!
He deflected the punch with the sword!
Three-sword style!
108 caliber phoenix!
It's enormous!
You're stronger than I expected.
The blade absorbed the slashes
of the other two swords into one.
It's impressive, but it still moves
a little too slow for my liking.
That just means I've got some work
to do before I can fully master it.
The increase in power
sure is nice, though.
Let's just hope I live long
enough to bring it under control.
You gave me one hell of
a sword, Samurai Ryuma.
You little guys are fast!
You could have put out my eye with that!
You runny bastard!
I'm gonna grind you down to go!
You can't spend the
entire fight dodging him!
Why'd he gotta be so big?
That was close.
Where is he?
I can't see with all the dust.
Three-sword style.
108-caliber Phoenix!
Come on, Zoro. Don't push it.
You're just making things worse.
Even if you do somehow miraculously
take him down, what's the point?
Luffy shadow's the only one
we'll get back from him.
We don't even have the
slightest idea where yours and
Sanji's are If we really
want to get our shadows back,
we just need to wait here
until Luffy takes care of it.
There's no point in killing yourself
trying to take down an undead giant.
All we got to do is believe in Luffy and
try to keep this guy busy for a while.
I've got plenty of faith in Luffy, but I'm
also aware of Luffy's one major weakness.
It's trickery.
They've got an invisible man, a girl who
controls ghosts, and a Shadow Master.
Trickery is the name of
the game on this island,
and they're all professionals at it.
It's safe to say that none of them is
planning on giving Luffy a fair fight.
I'm afraid that I must agree.
Yeah.
If they manage to stall Luffy and
the sun rises, then we're screwed.
Him, me, and the cook.
We'll melt until we're nothing but ash.
Maybe we can't save ourselves
but if we can get Luvia's
shadow back he can lay
this damn island to waste.
Looks like we got maybe
30 minutes before sunrise.
On the plus side that's
some thick fog the sun's
gonna have a hard time
getting through that.
So we're that close to dawn
we should count our blessings.
We've got this fog.
Can't say it's much comfort though.
The reality of melting Everything's
starting to sink in for me.
Huh?
How long have I been standing there?
What the hell?
What is this, an earthquake?
What's going on?
The ship's not anchored, remember?
We're caught in another bad
current like the last one!
Hey, the sky! Look up!
The sun's starting to come out!
And the fog why's the fog clearing
up what's happening please tell me
i'm wrong but do you Think we could
have left the florian triangle we
have and it's all because oars was
screwing Around with the helm earlier
ah you're right it's all his fault
why the hell do you have to go and do
That's Samurai!
We've got some serious stuff on!
Hello, Mark is coming born again!
We're on the moon and we've
broken out of the fog!
And it's all horse cult!
That's Samurai!
So what? Stop streaming! Who cares?
It's not the end of the world, you idiots.
We're pirates, aren't we?
The whole ocean is our home, no
matter where our ship ends up.
Yeah, but...
Time to shut your mouths.
I have the unexpected pleasure
of an important guest,
and you're rudely interrupting it.
So, Tyrant Kuma,
what can I do for the
only member of the Seven
Warlords who chooses to obey
the government like a dog?
The government considers you a valued
weapon in their arsenal of goons,
but I can't say I share their admiration.
I don't know what you're plotting,
but I'm sure that I won't like it.
If you were to take a vacation,
where would you want to go?
Come now, do I look like a fool?
I'm fully cognizant of the
powers you possess, all right.
Get to the point.
Did you come here to fight me or what?
Speak your business.
Why have you gone to the
trouble of seeking me out?
I'm here to deliver a report.
Well, let's hear it.
As you know, Crocodile has been removed
from his post as one of the Seven Warlords.
It's been decided who will replace him.
Yes, yes, yes!
Why didn't you say so?
And who have they chosen
as their successor?
sir.
There are hordes of pirates
that would kill for the job.
You might not have even heard of him.
His name is Marshal D.
Teach, also commonly known
by the name of Blackbeard.
Blackbeard, huh?
You're right, I don't know him.
He was a member of Whitebeard's
fleet, 2nd Division.
He's only recently proven his
abilities that led to his appointment.
I suppose the news hasn't
reached these foggy waters yet,
but his powers have raised a great
deal of commotion throughout the world.
Have they?
What was the original
bounty on his head? Zero.
How impressive.
A total unknown.
I'm surprised that the government
approved him for the job.
Yes, yes, yes.
They're probably happy they managed to
find someone to fill the spot so quickly.
I expect that this is supposed to restore
the balance of power or whatever, right?
Perhaps.
But if I were to place a bet, I
would say it's the exact opposite.
Never mind that, though. Huh?
There is an issue we must discuss, something
the world government is anxious about.
After the catastrophic
events at Annie's lobby,
they're more concerned than ever about the
movements of the Straw Hat pirate crew.
If they're following the log from
Water 7 headed toward Fishman Island,
there is a high probability that
they will find their way here.
If that's the case,
then I'm sure you can understand what
the world government is worried about.
It's the balance of power.
The government is concerned the Straw Hats
will take out another one
of the seven warlords.
That would be most unfortunate.
You better be joking.
Do they think I'm not up to the job?
I've never been so insulted in my life.
They sent you here to protect me
against those pathetic nobodies!
If you think my assistance could benefit
you, I'd be happy to help if you but asked.
Just who the hell do you
think you're talking to?
You bastard!
Have you even seen their
crew a bunch of crackpots
led by a rubber doll
and you honestly don't
think that i can handle
them no battle is 100
guaranteed do you know what
transpired at Enies Lobby
no one expected rob lucci
to lose and i'm sure
he wasn't expecting it
either let me see if i get
this straight the
government's so scared of the
Straw Hats that they want
to pit two of the seven
warlords against them huh
they only send me here
to warn you i was given
no specific orders to
offer you any assistance
then i recommend you
stay out of my damn way
buddy and if they want some
kind of report you can
tell them this this straw
hat that's got the
government swirling their
bridges i've already dealt
with him that means i
stole his shadow made it
a part of my zombie army
The fog
Could it get any worse?
That fog was our last hope.
There's nothing left to block the sun now!
Perfect.
The fog cleared up at
the worst time possible.
I'm really not looking forward
to the sun melting my face off!
I didn't know it was such
a beautiful night out.
It's Moria!
Moria? What? Where? What?
You're kidding, right?
Don is just around the corner.
Do you think this is the best time
for you to be standing around?
Wait, how are you here?
What happened to Luffy?
Huh?
I'm here, Master, but I can't see him.
Explain this, Usopp.
Just where the hell are you seeing Moria?
Look up, you idiots!
He's right there! The belly!
Inside Horst's belly!
Inside his belly!
He...
he is!
But where's Luffy?
Aw, don't tell me they
tricked him after all.
Or he's done for.
Don't you ever say Luffy's
done for! Uh... sure.
I don't get what's going on.
How come I can't hear Master's
voice, but I can't see him? Huh?
Is that some kind of
cockpit or something? Crazy!
Has there always been a cockpit in there?
All right, you pathetic
Straw Hats, here I am.
You wanted a chance to
fight me, you've got one.
And if you prove yourself
skilled enough to defeat me,
I'll release all of the shadows.
Go ahead and come at me all at once.
But you'll have to take down Ours, too.
That's the only chance you've got
to pull me out of this cockpit.
Now, that's cheap.
You're not fighting fair!
The only way to defeat Ours
is to defeat Moria first.
But how the heck can we do that
with him inside his stomach?
This narrows our target down to one.
Quit complaining.
Can't get cold feet now.
Hey you saw that little
pinch didn't work earlier
so you're gonna have to
find a mountain of salt.
Our only chance is to purify that monster.
We'll try to weaken as much
as we can until you get back.
Yeah okay I got it.
I'll be right back.
If I remember correctly there's a kitchen
somewhere at the front of the mansion.
They should have lots of salt there.
I should have figured as much.
The first thing they're trying to
do is get their hands on some salt.
Oh you hear that better?
Make sure long nose there doesn't
make his way to the kitchen.
You might as well take out
the entrance to the mansion.
Did
he get him?
This is bad.
With Merde inside.
Oars that idiot actually has a brain now.
Usopp!
Answer me!
Where are you?
He's perfectly fine!
I thought we might need a hefty quantity
of salt, so I rounded some up. Crook?
That was a close one.
Were you expecting someone
else to rescue you?